How are you, sir?
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Prayer And Deliverance In Jesus' Name.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Who are you?
I am a big man!
You are a big man?
Yes! A lot of power.
A lot of power?
Ok, come here.
No, big man!
Yes, big man!
Go on your knees before I talk to you!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Prayer And Deliverance In Jesus' Name.
Your back on the floor!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Somebody who needs deliverance is telling me he is a big man.
A big man in the kingdom of darkness.
Can you see your big man?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Zero big man! He is delivered.
He even hangs one leg up.
Not only that he is delivered, he is being hung.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Big man, stand up!
Set Free In Jesus' Name.
You are free.
I say, "You are free".
Thank You, Jesus!
Go there.
Thank you.
Are you a big man now?
I don't know!
I don't know, sir.
I'm free!
You said you were a big man.
No, I didn't say anything.
Ok. You can be going, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Thank You, Jesus.
I'm free!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
I am Lawrence Kazungu Kilabo.
I am from Kenya, cost, Mombassa.
I used to be a counsellor, a ward representative in my area.
Before, I was working with a tourist company.
I come from a poor family.
My father was a prison officer.
He married four wives and every wife had ten children.
That is why I come from a poor family background. Before that
my father told his wives to feed themselves and their children.
So, life became very difficult for us.
That was why every mother moved out to the interior to look for food for her children.
That was why, after my education, I got a job with African Safari Club as a guide supervisor and waiter.
There, I started exhibiting bad character - sleeping with women, ten women in a day.
I was very strong.
Then, I was called a star man. Star
Then, I used to sleep with three, five or ten women after their arrival because I was organizer of arrivals.
Right now, I have twenty-five kids in different countries.
There are ten mothers; some are in the UK, USA, Israel, Colombia, India.
I was really a star then.
I used to visit witch doctors to seek for powers.
They gave me charms which I rubbed on my palms.
Whenever I fell in love with a woman, I would approach her, say, "Hi", and shake hands.
Then, she would look for me and in one or two days, she would come to me.
When she came, I would be ready.
I would just touch her and kiss her and that would be the end of her story.
I used this power to attract women and womanise - it was my life then.
Later, I went into politics and used my evil powers to gain positions: counselor.
During the last election, I wanted to become a member of parliament.
I consulted witch doctors but things did not go well..
It is really hurting me but I will try.
One day, I was in Tanzania and saw a witch doctor.
I told the witch doctor that I would like to win that seat or else, we would fight.
He told me not to worry that everything would be fine.
Before I left, he called on his gods and they appeared -
some as snakes, some as donkeys and some with human faces.
We sat together in the bush, talking with them.
We agreed and left and I went to my country.
So you physically saw these spirits?
I physically saw them - not only seeing them but talking with them.
I agreed with them but they failed to get me the parliamentary seat.
I spent about 50 million Kenyan Shillings.
At the end of this, I was having 74,000 in my account and I didn't go through.
This made me to change my mind and I began to ask myself, "What will I do for my future?"
So, I sat down with my wife and we chatted.
I thank my wife because she was the one who introduced me to Emmanuel TV.
Mr Lawrence Kazungu Kilabo
Deliverance Testimony
She told me more about Emmanuel TV.
I touched the screen as Prophet T.B. Joshua was praying for the viewers.
That was why about three weeks ago, I decided to come here and meet the prophet.
I used to see Prophet T.B. Joshua on Emmanuel TV, not physically.
While Prophet T.B. Joshua was ministering, I was seated at the left side of the church.
He came over to me, touched me and I fell down.
I was on the floor for about 20 to 30 minutes and never knew he would come back to me.
He came back to me and with a nice voice said, "Brother, stand up. How are you?"
I said, "Fine".
After that, he touched me again and I fell; I did not know what happened after that.
Ok. So at that moment when he prayed for you,
you can't remember what happened at that point?
I don't remember at all.
He touched me and I fell down.
I didn't know what was going on.
Afterwards, I saw myself standing and people started singing.
Since last Sunday til now, people of God, wherever you are,
just look at me and see how strong and healthy I am.
It's a miracle.
To me, it's a miracle.
I have changed - everything.
No spirit comes to me to ask me anything because they know I'm in the House of the Lord.
Mr Lawrence Kazungu Kilabo
Deliverance Testimony
I am really healthy.
At this point, sir, give us a word of advice.
You said you were someone that all your life, you have visited witch doctors,
consulted powers from the darkness and today, you are here in the light.
What is your word of advice concerning that to our viewers all over the world?
Oh, yes.
I would like to tell people all over the world, if there is a man like me, Lawrence,
please just come over here; you will get your blessing without fear.
I was really in the dark.
But today, my eyes are opened now.
Mr Lawrence Kazungu Kilabo
Deliverance Testimony
Nothing will change my life; I will keep on singing and praising the Lord in this House forever.
Mr Lawrence Kazungu Kilabo
Deliverance Testimony
For those who are still looking here and there, I was there, talking with the devils and ghosts.
My friend, what are you waiting there for? Just come.
Mr Lawrence Kazungu Kilabo
Deliverance Testimony
Thank You, Jesus!
We thank God for your life, sir. We pray God will give you the grace
to continue to maintain this deliverance by making the Word of God the standard for your life
and we know the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.
Amen! Thank You, Jesus!
TT: Mel Flowers 14/08/2018 RV: Esther Mwelwa 14/08/2018